Evil has many faces. He has seen them all.
The Flock is a crime, drama, mystery film directed by Andrew Lau Wai-Keung.
Erroll Babbage has spent his career tracking sex offenders and his unorthodox
methods are nearly as brutal as the criminals he monitors.
When he links one of his deranged parolees to the disappearance of a local girl, he and his
new partner must scour the S&M underground to find her before it's too late.
Erroll Babbage, played by Richard Gere.
Allison Lowry, played by Claire Danes.
Viola Frye, played by KaDee Strickland.
Bobby Stiles, played by Ray Wise.
Edmund Grooms, played by Russell Sams.
Beatrice Bell, played by Avril Lavigne.
The Flock is a 2007 American thriller film directed by Andrew Lau,
the co-director of the Infernal Affairs trilogy.
The film, which marks his first English-language film,
stars Richard Gere and Claire Danes.
The film explores themes of pornography, trailer park,
kidnapping, new mexico, investigation.
The tone is intense and mind_bending and dark.